followupboss.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy - Follow Up Boss

##### Effective Date: July 9, 2014

## Purpose of the Privacy Policy.

Enchant LLC, doing business as FollowUpBoss.com (“Company”, “we” or “us”) provides  
a platform and tools to enable clients (“Clients”) to handle lead management and response  
for the real estate industry (“Service” or “Services”).

We are committed to respecting the privacy rights of our Clients, and we created  
this Privacy Policy to give you notice of how your private information will be used by us in  
connection with our Service. This Privacy Policy provides information on our policies and  
procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal and/or confidential  
information we receive from (1) Clients (including any third parties that submit information  
to us on behalf of Clients) and (2) visitors who simply browse our web site (“Visitors”).

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any  
material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult  
this policy regularly for any changes.

## 1\. What Information Do You Collect and How Do You Collect It?

At various times, you could be asked to provide information such as your name,  
title, company, email address, contact phone number or other information. Information  
collected is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable:

  1. Anonymous Information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a  
specific individual. For instance, we may know that thousands of people have visited  
this Privacy Policy, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or  
their date of birth. What we collect from visits such as this constitutes anonymous  
information. Some of the individuals who access our Services decline to use the  
personalization features that are available to them, and therefore those individuals are  
anonymous to us and the only data we collect about them is anonymous information.
  2. Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us  
specifically who you are, such as your name, email address, or phone number. Registering  
for or using a Service may allow the Company to “recognize” you to allow us to  
personalize our service for you.

### Anonymous Information

As is true of most applications and web sites, we gather certain information (such  
as mobile provider, operating system, etc.) automatically and store it in log files. We use  
this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer  
the application, to track users movements around the application or web site and to gather  
demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may link this  
automatically-collected data to certain Personally Identifiable Information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

If you are a Client, when you register with us via our Web Site, we will ask you  
for personally identifiable information, such as your first and last name, company name,  
title, email address, billing address, credit card information and password information for  
your email accounts. You may review and update the personally identifiable information in  
your profile by logging in and editing such information in your dashboard. If you decide to  
delete all of your information, we may cancel your account.

In addition, in connection with our Service, you may upload your private data or  
have third parties upload your private data to our Service. Given the confidential nature of  
the business information and data which may be uploaded in connection with our Service, we  
will treat this confidential information in the same manner as we treat personally  
identifiable information. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law  
or for reasonable business purposes in connection with our provision of Services.

Depending on the services you have chosen to use, some or all of your Personally  
Identifiable Information may be used by us to provide Services. Personally Identifiable  
Information may also be provided to intermediaries and third parties who assist us with the  
Services. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, however, we will not rent or  
sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties without your permission. No  
third parties will directly collect personally identifiable information through our web site  
or Service.

We do not honor “Do Not Track” requests through your web browser because the data  
we collect is necessary to improve security, to generate reporting statistics and to improve  
the user experience with our Services.

Enchant LLC is the owner of the information collected through the Service,  
provided however that you remain the owner of all business information and data uploaded to  
our Service.

### No Information Collected from Children

Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under  
the age of 13. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal  
information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately removed  
from any access. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such  
information to use or to disclose to third parties. Company has designed this policy in  
order to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”).

## 2\. How Do You Use Individual Information?

**General Use**. For Clients, we use personal information to provide the Services and contact Clients regarding account activities, new  
version and product offerings, or other communications relevant to the Services. If you  
contact us by email or by filling out a registration form, we may keep a record of your  
contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information  
that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you. In addition, we may use the  
personal information described above to send you information regarding the Service. If you  
decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information or communications  
from us, you can access your account and remove any personal information, but this may  
result in the closure of your account. The circumstances under which we may share such  
information with third parties are described in part (4) below.

## 3\. How Do You Store My Personal Information?

### Storage of Individual Information

Company operates or leases secure data networks protected by industry standard  
firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically  
reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only specially authorized individuals have access to  
the information provided by our Clients. Notwithstanding such measures, Company cannot  
guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally  
accessed and the individual information on them stolen or altered.

### Third Party Hosting, Serving and Storage.

COMPANY MAY CONTRACT WITH A VARIETY OF THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS/PROVIDERS/VENDORS  
FROM TIME TO TIME, TO PROVIDE FOR COMPANY’S HOSTING, SERVING, STORAGE AND TELECOMMUNICATION  
NEEDS, ETC., INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION STORAGE OF OUR USERS’ PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE  
INFORMATION. COMPANY SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE, AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL  
RESPONSIBILITY AND LIABILITY, FOR CULPABLE (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION NEGLIGENT) ACTS OR  
OMISSIONS BY ITS THIRD PARTY SUPPLIERS/VENDORS.

## 4\. Do You Disseminate Any Personal Information?

### Service Providers

We may use third parties to help operate our applications and Services and to  
deliver products and services, and may share your Personally Identifiable Information with  
our affiliates, service providers, vendors, suppliers, and other third parties that provide  
products or services for or through this Service (such as Web Site or database hosting  
companies, authentication providers, address list hosting companies, e-mail service  
providers, analytics companies, distribution companies and other similar service providers  
that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not  
have any right to use the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them beyond what  
is necessary for them to assist us.

### Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of  
interest in, and use of, our Service, our applications and send e-mails to third parties in  
the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not  
describe or identify any individual user.

### Complying with Legal Process

Company reserves the right to use or disclose your Personally Identifiable  
Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to  
otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the  
event you violate or breach an agreement with Company. Company will use and disclose your  
Personally Identifiable Information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of  
Company, its owners, or those of Company’s other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose  
your Personally Identifiable Information if we believe it is necessary to share information  
in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected  
fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or  
property, violations of Company’s other policies, or as otherwise required by law when  
responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes.

### Business Transitions

In the event Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger,  
acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets as well as in the  
event of a bankruptcy, assignment for benefit of creditors or receivership, your Personally  
Identifiable Information may be disclosed and will likely be among the assets transferred.  
You may be notified thereafter via prominent notice on our Company web site for 30 days of  
any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. Company further  
reserves the right to disclose, transfer or sell your personal information to companies who  
are affiliated with Company in Company’s sole discretion.

## 5\. Do You Allow Foreign Use Of The Service?

To the extent that you are accessing our Service in the United States while  
domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Personally Identifiable  
Information you are providing Company may be collected and stored in the United States and  
elsewhere and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the  
information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States and elsewhere.

## 6\. If I have Questions Concerning This Privacy Policy?

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us  
at support@followupboss.com.
